ever wanted to explore the world's most
exciting mega cities
while you may not be able to travel to
these places right now your money can it
can help you earn relatively attractive
returns over a medium to long term from
investments in these thriving real
estate markets
introducing mahindra manulife asia
pacific reits fof an open-ended fund of
fund scheme investing in manulife global
fund asia pacific reit fund
now ride the wave of a booming asia
pacific real estate market for an
investment as little as rupees 5 000
with a diversified asia pacific reach
portfolio of the master fund that
includes underlying assets such as
industrial parks data centers health
care centers offices
retail malls and hotels you get an
opportunity to gain not just from steady
rental income but also from potential
increase in the property prices across
the asia pacific region
the new fund offer opens on 28 september
2021 and closes on 12 october 2021.
for more information contact your mutual
fund distributor now
[Applause]
[Music]
mutual fund investments are subject to
market risks read all scheme related
documents carefully